The BE.
The best.
That. That will be and I keep
it that I don't think I.
Lose. I once went like
auction house or. Now. I figure
to live in
a home I'm. Going to aim to paint when
you're doing this because I had one of them
get it. To you live you believe Carson
you know when you have family but we are
getting spice to much just. Fine if you
get my piece of cake OK. I'm going.
To be trying to sold out of the need to
be white when it's coffee face one of us
government says he must have both you know
we were just talking about are you going
to say it was his turn to stay behind
this time you were thinking of taking his
place with me you know isn't saw some of
the stuff stable I know they're having
tonsils authority which one John let me
repeat my mama didn't believe in you know
we're going to fix this now let's see you
already be on option I mean yes. How
about taking he doesn't want to sing it
to me oh what about the tiara here and
yourself. You know as well as I do that
Mike's getting ready to sleep and have to
be met in my sorrow you too in just waiting
for the first time to come which is not
my fault something always happens to
interfere Yes Well nothing is going to
interfere this time it's not
company going to Motown. Should.
It didn't all this time do
you know. I like to take
a look at the video does not again because
it is simply. Obvious he was one himself
and put him down for this one to take no
notice of my just because he's my life you
get to do what he's done his job and you
can lump it yet again or cut yourself feel
Canada are cheesy anybody
can pick up Monday marks on
a factory stage still jellyfish and
a nice piece of work was hopelessly works
and I think she really should be good for
that attended an exposure which you know
why I was talking to Dusty. Funded I'm
going to now can get
a female under forty in my village Why don't
you pose of belief. Your lungs make me
sick I just think about the leave the
females not dames Homewood with all we have
the physical pact with Iraq you expect your
sickness but when you look what are you
why not. No press. Don't
use that all depends
a bit on this trip you would have and if
they lived I don't need money to enjoy
Miley we don't need much anyway I develop
more than forty hours like that on my
mind but if you by going to work forty
hours go. Down when you're really saying.
Attention on McCain I think.
I have. A couple of.
Years just attend. The hell
you work with no more go.
No longer go play not
that I need to pick. The
one want to. Get me going to. Another
way where you're seeing with.
No one feel. For the skipper.
While the violence. Fish and
chips so. I did
a pink indeed I was going to
be very nice to anybody. Yet
I'm using a cup said No
culture is going to be just
a day left. And today I'm the guy
good the oh man good how the bank
balance. I have to manage on
the day I was in cash you drank I want
you to ring me seem all yes and make
a date for lunch tomorrow get
a four pound box of chocolates
four pound box of there is
a war on your nose is that I haven't seen
much of it lately or your influence today
yes but to see to the hidden in the evening
and table of the binoculars Yes Now
today Miss Cutter now and I
mean this David thank now and
hang on to make your mind up ready. For
me over the present day Kyla thanks the
rest with you tomorrow yeah bye. If you
do balloons and even the elementary
instincts of gentlemen. Let's not tick
off you've got to die yes or no that's
something I want to see me about I want to
see the tenant Brace I'm afraid he's not
here anything I can do. Right. Now to do
well despite Petty Officer I was leaves
or somebody's got to stay and take his
place Yes I think it's arranged William
stays Yes Or well that's just to see it's
very hard on for William asserted with
his domestic problems her and his two
youngest in hospital syringes manager. Oh
yes sir how else do you have two youngest
are you not offering to forego your
own leave by any chance I. Said
but I thought you were
getting married and had
a TEAC cold feet Oh no sure there isn't
a nice regarding Nanda Sir
just that. Well you think
a man shouldn't rush metro in the like quite
agree and I think I like just to think
it over
a bit longer assertion or. They
mostly act fix it thanks for. Own
P.R.
I don't help and I want to
seem like having you. Come
in but you haven't come in.
I wanted to have
a talk with you want to flame
you don't know that if you know
I've often wondered about you
often my you haven't done
a little higher in the service I
mean you knocked about the world
a bit speak up the language
isn't what I seem to fit in
a man like you should
be Is life just because
that counts not to let me know about it
off I think the best thing I can do is to
him to you don't have to read that to know
what's in it about your wife he wants
a separation I'm gonna stick to his fish
and chips and get out of my business yes
I'm trying to agree with you I don't like
the sound of your brother in law. On the
other hand you can hardly blame him if your
wife does time to separate is that out
of the house the whole time of C.
. I give him so much leeway because you
went down again and you lost me for the
most of that I'm sure she goes of the
dead listen anyway if I were you I'd
try and get him savor this time and the
wife will probably get on the band of hope
to please anyone singing fish and chips.
My wife once operations are going to have
it
is that what you really want to
say yes or something else now
that's all I can
be doing oh that's my
cousin if we threw me
oh. The oh oh I have no. I
want to go to show yes they always
say that the happiest day of
a man's life is the day before he gets mad
at you know that's right I mean the day
before your marriage is the funniest
thing in the world for students
a lot like collagen especially
when you get to marry
a skinny girl like out it
and I'm going try to do
a self sometimes I mean what I thought
well that's different to you Mike Mike
Mike your mind is down this you know this
fake gun you know because I think you
know when I was coming here you were fixed
to give the students when you're going
to do it I mean not on that list and that's
beside the point now naturally enough
for me but there must be
a mistake there's no mistake you can save
yourself it's not all right but I can't
believe that everybody knows I was going
to get married tomorrow I got anybody in
this ship that wanted to leave or some is
going to be done about it. For us and or
there's no order every time we try to fix
something up something happens to support
us what are power to fifty K.
Things in the hands of an all seeing faith
that's what we are you know I think
before and I don't you want to
fix it all sort of it but P.P.I.
.
But when we come back and you should really
get comfortable with something really
got you what about to leave for did you
see the traditional one going to sure but
that's right I knew you would mind staying
on the show but yeah you know put it on
the novel's place I knew you wouldn't
mind mapping of the car park you know if
there were no damage that could be put out
but I would ask you to do something for
nothing.
Like I could pick just over here to take
a plane come on the boat just leaving I
can't go like this. I have got my kid
that's all right now
dropping off come on out of.
Keep up the beer. With me about the.
Bet out of one on the
whole trip. How long.
Seven. Never been up.
The you.
Want to make.
Up.
The shop.
That was
a Sunday morning is the only time we have
free you know except for us like get off
the T.V. On wins to lose remedy
that I'm going to. Try to pick
a fight and he would not make it's important
when this leak goes in this leak and I
put to get around to it and I. Wish I could
get the same trying to kick out and I
tell you fellows get sim days leaves and
you know that means just start the day and
I mean maybe. Oh.
I know my darling how I don't run the whole
thing out from you again I said Friday
. This is browning Depor ship yeah bad
news I'm afraid on that order from
Captain has to pull back and once of course
I'm very very cold as the sea tired to
charge and get this done right away. How
do I know man probably want to make up
a Ford bridge Now listen there's a train
leaving London the two fifteen that makes
a connection of all right all right you can
look it up yourself then but you've got
to be back here by nine
o'clock at the latest right.
And I'm. At
a first day of my. First I had four
months off the probable leave can phone
the fact that after all the time like on
the wall of dates I think everything blown
sky high top of the top C.E.O.
Job who could not. Spend all that time
getting all those one day to take
a Pentagon the next I write my boy I had
to fight against that sort of thing all my
life by.
I think it does to my boy. Think you
know we're special Next check out what
a temple coming up then and it's
a stone you take your training.
You watch me setting.
I mean
a chair I need to point the very best
all right that's them rather. Well. You
know man would be just saying I got
some bad news for you the report of
a Super Media Player. When he
does
a joke it's no joke it's an order your
sermons and I'm going to. Say and all was
good but I don't. Look at
the bill I know you agree.
To run the same old dogfish what have you
come for. That's what who doesn't want to
see that's she's out all right all right
I can wait in the meantime I have
a few choice words for you.
You know often don't make
a scene consciously I'm busy all
the East Coast OK OK I'll give you
a hand don't know about I don't know well
just missed it I think I may have to come
up with
a. Service that I like serve
it. To good for the brain.
To do the next to. Me.
You. Know Not really I look at
you know all the time when I.
Was next. You know you are you come to me.
But you think that how
do you must somehow be
a nice. Letter. I brought
it home for you. Here.
The big picture because there's
a good. Just like. She's
going to come home sober just for
once to save enough time. OK
Also why don't you go keep out of this
going on with me both of you understand
don't you know we're not wanted the only
I could come over to talk to them I did
not mean in the same to me but they were
the model I was not having overcome. That
would mean that I had to do you have to
get off at night how do you get out.
Now they got going on yeah what's going
on you know it was right you got right up
to date we've done just a break
you don't do it you're leading
a team and games option. You know come back
they may then UNDERSHAFT under-sea his
wife and kids we wanted to. Talk about we
got to get back in shape so that anybody
want to think about you know I have.
No.
Good luck.
LOL LOL LOL LOL
LOL. We were
oh yeah that he would be.
And you never think here
next time you're going to got along the
trick go with often now yes now I right now
sure there's no Ari what you mean is no I
don't have blacks would like to change
places with you Mike and
I look at Charlie he won
a phantom splash so that's that. Just put
me on the post and say well they're still
out I'll talk to them I lose the right you
never catch me losing I think you know
more about the lady you brought if from
the facts shop well or better you didn't
see the car some guy in the scullery did
you know nod you don't burn them pretty
fingers you get
a game out of way Mr Dad how come Wolf
it's you know you've got you know
a lot of stink of that in ducky I think
I'll tell you Miss Hochul I mean I can keep
on calling Miss I'll call it sounds balmy
of course it does I think I think up to
his Uncle Ted do it right across
his chest Cicely as will be
a going already that I need time to be
helpful helpful your squinted to that's what
he did that he had given names to do you
know they were in books I wouldn't say all
over him but he's going to if you had to
keep going she wouldn't want to risk go on
show you something at the end of my wish
to school now do listen is the time to be
helpful miss what I can assure you
is the biggest part again I mean.
Not literary. It's given me in the
morning well you know I just. You know.
Now my prayer list of You look fine and
asked Has never thought phonetics no man I
want to talk to you at all oh you
know you haven't even if night come
often it's gray. And superstitions then I
was just reading your congregations when
it came down and the Rani
of for you. Alone I'm
a happy man you'd like to vote and don't
forget to name the first one after me I'm
female she's decided what it's going to
vary based wishers and don't forget to name
the first one so your uncle right
because they don't have twins Mike
told Peter Gunz mate and cutting the
return to ship. Sailing to imagine track
train that gets a recall.
Sounds like they may have
a look we want to give you
a ticket. Yes it's
a recall alright I was just
my luck. There must be some
mistake no human mistake then
the anyone what you mean it
David Souter waiting to Mike
are you getting it it's not my fault
we've been with all my force thanks to
Mike but I asked you can't
you also not of them I know.
I don't understand you mean by gave yourself
away I don't know you didn't by any
chance get something to send these
telegrams did you fuck me to
a thing like that is genuine All right
well boys you better be going going to
expects you now or you're in
a terribly hard to get rid of us aren't
you not friends now thanks Mark we've all
got to do our bit you're in your sub
and me and my reserved occupation it's
submarine to educate Mike and you Wilson
want for there's no recall for me Dicky
you don't expected to come here do yeah
come on get a move on and not so much of
a geeky there under the cops and orders
from there oh alright alright OP it well
obviously you have.
Come on Mike we've got
thing about it all night.
Now we are away and the next.
Our.
Engine will present I don't want to leave
Mr Cox For myself I would have thought it
was rough going to short for leave from the
Navy ran into my saw coming back to you
satisfied now what do you mean you choose
me to know telegram for I said there was
something fishy about it we're going to
think I feel about this I fixed up with her
my next leave you see if I
don't you expect to find
a waiting for you sitting on the doorstep
when you get back the lot you know about
our stamps OK will not be
OK in front of. The engine
a more talks yes but we filled up with three
from spare crew. What were you content
with against White could you know I could
not speak with orders to be confided to
nobody below the rank of oxygen.
And expects the rank and.
File and somebody to go to prison I
was. Going to. Look like something you
know you would have
a more interesting time Mr Tate. Thank
goodness and you can bring it off.
I hope I do have to buy them.
I think.
They go apart spring.
That's. All the time.
Maybe doctrines are just I mean
what I want to talk to the crew.
Here that you hear that their life
attacking. The captain speaking.
Well as you've probably guessed it's
a special job this time and right
now are. Back regularly back in for
a bright day we have the energy of
Lent and the new German battleship the
Brandenburg is about to leave then I have
been for the tribes in the boat. To get
to the Brandenburg or at the process of
actually working out. And to get to the
canal you have to hike because past cooktop
and everywhere back. We are expected to
intercept I think that. Now then one thing
more and I have been listening in the
engine room pretty much doing it right for
the first hour the most personally very
artistic thing to eat not in the heat that
it is also means we miss risk taking on
the service as much as we can even in
daylight. So every one of us will be right on
it. Every moment you don't you. At all.
If you.
Spot it.
Now one of. US is. Right. On the
service. That's all like you said
when we started and we were on.
Our merry little water.
OK. But I do love you.
Always thinking that you will be
needing this ring if you want to do
a little deal. Going to cause you
have been eating it if you. Like
but you never get in the way I don't like
the idea of marriage and what's more the
bride and you didn't. Have to look far to
see the reason why and look at the piano
. Like you why didn't you see the wind.
He was trying to do my wedding
ring for this girl let's use.
This girl naming the girl of that list.
Of the. Look she gave me when we were
leaving what you're trying
to do three pinch at
a pinch and she knew that this man was all
right if he gives you any trouble you
can easily buy off the boxes the guy.
The. Rescue boys.
Anybody about them. And then
number four see him again and.
They'd come get him. If
you know anything and.
Be watching. Him. So if you're reading
a bit of that area. Ha
ha ha ha ha ha.
International law I can pretend. I'm
from that. You want to go is using
a radio to give us away I'm sorry we
chopped down the aerial before you get
anything through. This.
I'm not.
On the way. Christmas party
to come up and I got
into. My.
Pickup. But.
It was just
a fantasy Chuck used. By. People
not. Most of the you should be
Wednesday and these will be part of
news itself and if I get
it from. Me Oh make
a Brownie have you gotten
enough of it is that
a lot about. This craft code. So.
We don't know one of the would you know
about that girl you know not to me because
a man's just remember he suggested I should
show up this year but that's just what
I'm going to do and it's not going to read
the same I suppose you get your telling
off nothing changes Oh is that what you
want to know part of what we have you can't
expect anybody to water nearly into
Arabella Arabella so that's so nice but the
girl in the fags shop but I thought
that's the one like that's right you know
Annabella it's going to
cost anything to obliterate
a bit let alone mean I already own my whole
life all right the mission has taught
me to spell you can use some of these
of the like when I go into a B.
But i already in front of you have it once
put it from the design I'll give you.
That I figure that's just about how much
you love her which will start to work as
soon as the changeover comes. Get some
more stuff to do something about this time
I to be to speak up and I know there's
a battleship or two after
all right. Inside of you.
Or your. Wonderful Brandenberg
that's kind of cheating.
And it's finding what was going
to keys it's. OK I mean I'm
down right. Now for
not telling how hot stocks fall
it's not. Supposed to come in.
Group down. The
big. Brother.
Scraping the minefield cable.
Will both. Know mission it
became sort of the bomb because
he. Only needed to lift on
a. Look at the back of.
The BE. So we got.
Lucky to get. There with. His
mother of my. Life if you will do.
What you're worrying about.
The part of the business that is on the
end of the day before. Then I think of
times. Square and then
eventually turn back.
Time to get it and actually throw it
into the body. Of the live as manager
something that I didn't tell
many things that I didn't let on
a new journey. The book
I mean. I've got.
Just about going into. That
because you comfort him up.
And down. Ask him available
time say that's bogus out.
That we can talk. With you just
like yes I'm not jealous or.
No this money should be
a killer. Right
.
Well. The Bamberg. Probably
well inside if you know I know.
You're going to trip so. You know.
We're going after. The hell
smacks of the net the spirit of John's
a reality on the surface and she can do.
Right.
By. Oh I could go get my good car.
What are you feeling.
Now you know one five.
Come to be more careful Rowlings when you
complain because the weather. Is building
the old ones are the breaks the time. And
death in which men do women. Steady.
Not to get cross with
a lot of these days up spin it up and
over the top of this torture but it never
been like that it's been
a pleasure doing you slain. OK
I don't know I might used as bait on
my next meet nice piece of work for
a nice piece of work
a. Job or not could not be made
from UPS I didn't get it I lost it
I'm not I thought something Iraq. I've
got plenty more of this stuff and if you
want to make another something better to
do with my time to make the watch for
taunting. You John I'm going
to make. This rain I think.
Balance how I live it is really
getting to the stuff and you guys.
I mean you know like I'm. Pretty
a bit. Lost in
a lot of what you call
of the wanted me. But
. I think I did listen. For all of
us three he's four yes looks
like tell me how game
has to ring going all right all
right. Bella's long name isn't it.
But I'm going to Gladys. And trap him you
know your day you were saying something
about say being interested in that
piano. Oh yes I think she just wanted
a music night that's all just
think so. Close it's all
a tease. But
it. Was it was
a. Scam they got. Still
.
So I. Am
right. Next to
a team of I. Full
of stand together.
All I'm telling an honest guy.
With
a bigger. That's
a very we get through next time you know
me I don't even down seven days but I
actually got out.
Of it if you are.
Just going to do it and it really telegraphed
last last night and then discover you
got work agreement and you might find our
joke about. That. But I had to get it.
Among them right now so.
I see.
No sign of the ships.
Kind of
a week away thing and I see Tiger.
Now as the Brandenburg. Always
never see other.
Ethnic.
Come to the way I think of. Well
in and I trained as I have some.
Things. That we don't and
out of education thanks.
Simon I'll.
Have more about. How do you think
that yourself they like now for.
Still feel like fish and. Chips here.
Stop it stop the fifteen. Fifteen
a stop and also. The more. She
goes of course you're going to.
Get. Stopped out of. Town. No
matter what I thought.
I don't I'm not going to say yeah but it's
a real thing that I just because the
captaincy that we clash I'm not I think it's
a roundabout and I'm not big
with this much I don't trust me.
Enough dogs know what maybe
a scream you're getting anything
else. In it you know not to own
it if you're getting any.
Place late.
Here the man and I. Love all of
you for ends now of all tubes
and I want to I want you all to you on the
run you must be the old brandy balls are
self. Too much right out of my.
I know that I. Can. Get.
Right. Back.
Confounded number one Don't think about
it like opinion of blasted drum.
And if they're being. Read it somebody
had green for us in being four.
And seven degrees on have thought about
seven degrees you know eight No twelve
No I can't these really understand
straight I'm looking at them make it
a beat on about range damage or
number one Can't you keep the basket level
for five seconds down and it's going to
. Let me know when you have some sort of
a trim as to race. Color
in seven. To from here.
To rise coaxingly. Ring on
there go. From tell me.
You're not going to. Stop the
bump. I said stop the bloody pump
you keep awake. Steady
at thirty five feet so.
How they see are. Very green six or.
Seven degrees on have thought about seven
degrees on four car but it was cool to
six. Range. SIMKIN minutes in high
powered. Or other points
a. Speed star with the
speed thought it sucked.
Distrusting. You getting in the
house I'm not asking. You.
Because if we've got it on a plate then by
a two step setting stand by all to use down
the ends that's going to pull out then
by all tubes. Don't forget I told you
number to go through the True same as if we
were in blockhouse creek. Might keep your
eyes nice reservoir pressure OK blinking
give him primping my game and when he knows
it from some like you may stand by I
will do you know what off. I
should go you keep it beside
this leave it to me because he gives you
all of us and I get it see. You know I
know what it is. I do
I'm very green sick so
doing to myself no revolutions
steady on or whatever. She is one
lovely bad kid very great success
range twenty three minutes
fifty degrees on the porch about. To be
number one fifty so strange three thousand
people speed of roughly thirty knots that
a bit much make it ten twenty five right
think of it up here way take that is go.
Down. I remember any any time times.
Bearing on grapes expansion
that need to be done about.
Destroy. The screen fifteen hundred
yards. I was going to become
a. Stand by to take it on the number one
we've got to close. Yours all tracks
so on the same course right.
Well.
The stuff I'm going to give to the afterlife
and yes I've been trying to. To pretty
. Good. I was just getting and keep it off
a lot of my life home docs
and the Bible and say.
Angle seventeen degrees. Seventeen degrees
and by then by and by.
Five I'm. Going to.
Go. Take stuff because
that's all six clinics.
They got down on the. Stand by that.
Something I don't know about
I. Should have been talking
a few seconds and. You
are right down the Milan stuff but not
mounds of doing and playing the hand getting
painted hands up on one hand he quite
a bit in the back and one if we did and I
think often what it's letter it's hard to
tell with the job just.
To look for my name so now take
a couple spankings you can come up and
bunch of money all right probably about to
die I want to know was how it
happened my time trust. Nor on get.
Something I read. Coming
this way. Greasing speed.
Coming into town. Thank you being down.
There by the best spin on what.
You.
Can somebody. Second
lighting. A ruckus and.
And I was speed so we don't understand
how they get up to get us up.
I think we can have whatever Become going
to touch on the right you know. Right OK
if you don't have the money really are.
You. Willing.
To Let. Him.
Play I mean I've got all the stuff in the
foreign builders all right to make. A
lot.
Still. Do what I can that
they might yet which is
a. Minute into it but I think the patience
that oh you take my place they're going
to come in.
I don't to be worried by
them. I never was anybody.
Crazy is finished I.
Used other parts of the cab OK.
So Philadelphia is at this right. Now one
each and we got forty so close drinking
among the other
a lot. Getting the. Meeting
faster. Getting peace in the. Lead not.
That was our walk to get
a job or the pressure. Not to continue
rising What were you thinking at German
prisoner Oh yeah I'll take that later. You
look at all the current. What the couple
said if we keep the market up for another
I will approach the back of it as they
can keep me at it I shan't come again to
attempt again. To make the market
in. The last week constant
feeling weak suites also want to. Go for
a look at the magazine next to the
star surely I know you'll find
a good long life such as being the.
Young chap that must buy can start and
if I think that in fact the Bush delusion.
About losing the oil we must be leaving
a trace of it on the surface let me enjoy
taxes so it's any question of time.
And I was saying that
a question of time before they hit the
bull's eye. You know until we get it think
we're like God I'm going to keep.
Talking and. I want.
No not yet we haven't already talked about
one poster to Britain that's not funny.
The only thing made up for that
one five zero watching. For
those papers in his pocket if that was
a little stopwatch to OK. That's
not going to be him. That's right
cops and why.
He would kill me I want to get want to
fight for yourself I didn't want to really
think of the gang along
I don't think I was
a farmer. And
he said yes I want to be number one
troops are not the greatest houses on the
course my choice but I think another two
for what I'm really good question I still
think they want to hang
on one thing that I saw.
Never
. Played all the buttons thought I was
taking Steve and I have to engineer the
captain but you have to stand in
a body it's. Like. Well.
One two parts are about once in about
a bumpy but you're like what I call
and I just quit you know. Neck
neck
watch out of my head together I know so.
Well that these.
Next studies believe the one
and I also stop lying on
that up tanks that I got out.
Next i.
Lead
to believe you have
a very cool. Witness my favorite. Court
and the ball hit me and I'm fifty. Feet.
I feel mom I'm
a great. You'll be ashamed of yourself
listening to that tech allows.
No missed was no news from the Atlanta
thanks so much still. Looking scratch
that So come on it will make you
a big curly. Option
What's the longest time you've ever
been down there last night if you put
a sock in the jaw of yours
and say Doxygen Jack.
I stand as. Soon as the willing
done my part of the bet is going to
fight for I haven't even
a cock head big hook Yank
I mean your arguments.
Yeah I'm OK Captain
speaking Well there's no need for
me to explain the situation to you
you all know it I take it.
You. Guys.
Mark check just about one
decent meal for the T.I.
. I've gone into the net at
a cafe and what I propose to do is this I
pretty much. I.
Get. OK.
Sorry it's come to this but
I'm afraid there's no agenda
thank you. Oh. Hell that's all
I can fart I want you to get me out. You
know what this means you turn for the rest
of the road you go perhaps that's
a prison camp in Germany go on cheer
us up bunch my concentration camp.
Thought I was
a. Really you are going to but I
think you might like to know the
right to research the question
of these times. I mean. I have
over. They wanted it wasn't just.
About you just me telling us.
I remember right here there's
a little vocal fry up on that and
if you go I call that once in about
a gram just before the war. Well when I was
thinking so hard to put it there these
days it is almost certain to be
are some of that I just have
a shot and I guess you can defy haven't
found out they are the land of the new I
mean they have
a freshness to glow you could bring in the
boat and they could hijack the juice if
you didn't get away with it we
couldn't be any worse off I
wonder if you know those jellies uniforms
I could get anything in that you thought
it or I have you have seen supposing you
were stopped what sort of story could you
tell. A plane might have crashed in the
sea with my mates killed never going to
show in the day but I know I don't have
to remind you that if you're caught in
a German uniform it won't just be
a question of being taken prisoner you know
I don't have nobody to treat energy as
an army. Going to be easy getting into
a strange however at night they take
a crack at it right hops and I pick up
some of the prisoners uniforms pick right
out and they write about dark I wish I
could come with you you are German man and
stand the stranger. Maybe
right or at houses Oh.
Thank you Hobson.
Goodies made. Monkey came monkey audience.
Games monkey York games monkey YORKA.
Hugo Charlie Charlie. Keep
shop about on I'm going
on.
Like I'm going to fix the.
Internet also I phone him.
For the show and the home.
I was just doing that was very similar.
Some of it I know that's what it upsets.
About to. Have
a catered learning. End of the pier eight
Feathers everywhere going to remember
everything that means
a good second it has kept
it going. I got punk. Rock
person right now what am I.
And she can i have my own and
thank you thank you I don't emigrate I'm
a. Fish. I know I do understand you
and I end up with the profit. Yes you
monkey equipment. That will come where you
are going to be forgiven I want to put.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh.
I don't know.
But you. Then do have hope.
Yeah of the vendor here from
a great finish. And if you.
Think. About you know we've arrived.
I don't know. I
think I'm alone. Then I Indians look out
for many probably close up. A lot of money
commandos. Know
that bit low to.
Nobility pretty stubborn twenty to fifty.
It's
a popular show and keep. The
campaign thank. You so much like
a little even client. If it happens. I go
this is the British Navy we want all
installs and we've no time to argue about it
it will be no argument the British Navy
is always welcome in Denmark now you are
talking what you want my men will
help you. And not get the bike I got.
One of them. Wait
a minute are you firing in short
Michael Holmes. I mean you're right
that's
a good man right that. I'm
having
a time. Machine gun. Right
now I.
Just hate telecom it's got
to do all right I can't.
Think of getting my own. Take three men
a backup copy on hang on to get one last
in the whistle and be back here helping
them so they can hold
a module Johnson because we want to reinvent
it I want to get tested but I thought
.
Look you know we're not giving
a green mama the money like. You
said.
That warehouse is full of or no phones
coming with it we want to call but if that
long comes up.
Right. I'll take over for
you no cause for panic.
I know how we going out. And I got
a lot more yet. You know my dad
asking what he's Gage is showing.
Right about. How much about going
out in the front of a bus. At
a time. I
mean. Twelve hundred gallons right now
risking I've got to Scott's caution and I'm
going to take
a shortcut. If you want to go. On
. I mean.
Look. Good.
Then and look.
Them up because I mean. It caused.
By.
Good.
I got. Returning. To.
Get that don't even seem to be.
Uplifted by being one of the.
Much relations. I. Think
a lot. Of the funding but. Not.
The way. We think abandoned
the got the. Money we.
Look at the Britain bit
see what we've got. To.
Put it up and it's. The back. To.
Basics of what.
I'm.
Grand job to make it better my fishing smack
your ready much abused was on my back
and let it go down. I just pushing off
so you have to wait for that dollar I
promised about Good luck and please
accept it thank you and nice when.
I. Die. I'm
not going to say you. And.
I know that I'm gonna.
Everything. You. Know you need
me well let alone the game. That
if you had to sometime like this
you.
I'll pay. It but you see it coming in.
You know she bought
a battleship with oh did you know
bottle that I've got fully. And
a team. Of
money. I'm.
Going to getting Oh. Well enjoy leave
this time I suppose you will be seeing it
on get all the men you know gone and you
going to war again I'm going to get
it to the end of them and there's
a saucer stuff going on.
One comes in another goes
out just like running on a bus.